truthinitiative.org 2017-04-21

# Privacy Policy | Truth Initiative

[www.truthinitiative.org](http://www.truthinitiative.org/) is a website of Truth Initiative, which is dedicated to achieving a culture where all youth and young adults reject tobacco.  We respect your privacy and have created this policy to explain what information we collect and how we use it.  If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us.

**General User Information**

We automatically collect aggregate information about our site’s users, including the domain name and IP address of visitors, the browser and operating system used, the date and time of each visit and the source of referral.  This aggregate information does not identify individual visitors, and it is used for our own research purposes and to improve the site’s content, structure, and security.  We share this information only with our vendors, who use it for the same purposes.

**Cookies**

Cookies are information files that allow websites to remember users’ activities on a website.  When you visit our site, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser.  We use the information we learn from cookies to improve the quality of our service, for example, by tracking user trends.  We share this information only with our vendors, who use it for the same purposes.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.  However, some of our features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**Personal Information**

If you choose to sign up for our newsletter or otherwise provide personal information on our site, we will use that information to customize and improve your website experience.  We share this information only with our own vendors, who use it for the same purposes.  Neither Truth Initiative nor its vendors will ever share your personal information with anyone else without your consent, except in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal processes or preventing fraud or imminent harm.  We will never sell your personal information.

**Opting Out**

We communicate only with those who have chosen to receive communications from us.  If you do not want to receive communications in the future, or would like to review personal information collected from you and request corrections, please contact us.  If we ever decide to use your information for a new, unanticipated use not previously disclosed in our privacy policy, we will post the policy change prominently on this page and provide you with the ability to opt-out of this new use.

**  Security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or disclosure or destruction of our users' data.  We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to perform their jobs.

**Questions**

Please contact us if you have any questions about this policy.
